Guide to Rice University Vice President of Finance and Administration office records, 1938-2010 UA 140
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VIII: Addendum: Dean Currie Finance and Administration
  - Administration (General)
    - Texas Medical Center Transportation Plan, 2002 (1 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Texas Medical Center Transportation Plan, 2002 (2 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - "Trees of the Rice University Campus", 1989 (P. A. Harcombe et al.) (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Trees, 1994-2000 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Athletics Administration and Finances
    - Athletics Correspondence, 1988-2002 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Athletics Finances, 1988-1993 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Athletics Finances, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Athletics Finances, 1995-2003 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Athletics: Facility Study, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Athletics: Faculty Council Report, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Athletics WAC Membership (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Athletics: WAC Information (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Athletics: NCAA Audits, 1994, 1995, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Athletics: Gender Equity, Title IX (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Athletics Graduation Rates (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - University Governance and Finances
    - Board of Governors Orientation, 1994, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Board of Governors Orientation, 1996, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Rice University Charter Amendment, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Council (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Rice Trust, Inc.: Policies and Procedures (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Rice Trust, Inc.: Board Meetings, 1990-1995 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Rice University Fund Council, 1989-1995 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - University Finances, 1996-2004 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Federal Awards, Fiscal Year, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Tuition (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - "Implementing 'Rice: The Next Century,'", 1997 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Committees
    - Athletic Review Committee Report, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Audit Committee, 1993-05 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Audit Committee, 1993-12 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee, 1994-02-1994-03 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee, 1994-05-1994-12 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee: Josephine Abercrombie Tribute, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee, Fiscal Year 1996 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Buildings & Grounds Committee, Fiscal Year 1998 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Campus Safety Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Campus Store Advisory Committee: By-Laws, Members, 1980-1991 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Campus Store Advisory Committee, 1981-1987 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Campus Store Advisory Committee, 1971-1977 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Campus Store Advisory Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Computer Planning Board, 1987-1992 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Computer Planning Board Report, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Computer Planning Board Report, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Computers, 1990-1991 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - External Affairs Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Financial Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Food & Housing Oversight Committee, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Fringe Benefits Committee, 1989-1995 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Gift Policy Review Committee, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Parking Advisory Committee, 1991-1995 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Policy Advisory Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - HR: Ad Hoc Faculty Committee on Retirement, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Rice Ring Committee, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - Security Review Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Staff Advisory Committee, 1992-1996 (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - Patent policies and technology transfer, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Facilities & Engineering (Now Facilities, Engineer, and Planning)
    - F&E: Building Projects, 1991-1999 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - F&E: Capital Planning, 1995- (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - F&E: Cogeneration Power Plant, 1986 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - F&E: Facilities Management, 1992-1996 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - F&E: Facilities Management, 1997-1998 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - F&E: Facilities Management, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - F&E: Facilities Management, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - F&E: Furniture (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - F&E: Internal Audit, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - F&E: Maintenance Shops, 1997 (photos) (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - F&E: Personnel (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - F&E: "Shades of Green....Environmental Design,", 1998 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - F&E Utility Cost, 1992-1997 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Food & Housing (Now Housing & Dinner)
    - F&H: Budgets, Actual and Projected, 1979-2010 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - F&H: Correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - F&H Colleges: Room & Board, Meal Plans, Parking, 1992-1999 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - F&H Colleges: 40th Anniversary Report, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - F&H: Colleges Master Plan and Director Search, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - F&H: Food Survey, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - F&H: Food Survey, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - F&H: Food Survey, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - F&H: Food Survey, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - F&H: Food Survey, 1995-1996 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - F&H: Flood of October, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - F&H: Habitat for Humanity, 1996-1997 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - F&H: Halogen Lighting, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - F&H: Handbooks, Off-Campus Housing Guide, 1989-1996 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - F&H: Marriott Proposal, 1987 (Box 115, Folder 28)
  - Human Resources
    - HR: Correspondence (various topics), 1993-2000 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - HR: Arthur Andersen Benefits Survey, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - HR: Benefits and Payroll Audit, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - HR: Compensation and Taxes, 1988-1996 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - HR: Compensation and Taxes, 1997-1998 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - HR: Minimum and Low-Wage Employees, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - HR: Towers Perrin Compensation Survey, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - HR: IRS "Intermediate Sanctions" (re-deferred compensation), 1998 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - HR: Domestic Partner Benefits (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - HR: Fringe Benefits, 1991-1995 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - HR: Fringe Benefits, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - HR: Fringe Benefits, 1997-2001 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - HR: Job Evaluation Study, 1992-1994 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - HR: Performance Appraisals System, 1982-1998 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - HR Policy Revisions, 1994-1999 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - HR: Policy Manual, 1995 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - HR: Monthly and Annual Reports, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - HR: Retirement Plan, 1989-1996 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - HR: Retiree Health and Life Insurance, 1995-1999 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - HR: Early Retirement, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - HR: Retirement Plan for Highly Compensated Employees, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - HR: Defined Contribution Retirement Plan, 1997, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - HR: Security-Sensitive Positions, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - HR: Service Awards, Retirees, 1993-1999 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - HR: Hewitt Workforce Reduction Survey, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - HR: Joslin Diabetes Center Retirement Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - University of Michigan Task Force on Retirement, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Princeton Faculty Retirement, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 28)
  - Campus Buildings and Facilities
    - Allen Center, 1964-2004 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - School of Architecture (Anderson Hall), 1988-1997 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Autry Court, Fox Gym (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Baker College Tower, 1993-1994 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Baker Institute Planning, 1992-1994 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Baker Institute: Building Plans, Space Allocation, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Baker Institute Fund-Raising, Budgets, 1993-1995 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Baker Institute Fund-Raising, Budgets, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Baker Institute Budgets, Fiscal Year 1994-Fiscal Year 2000 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Baker Institute: Prospectus, Growth-Breaking, 1993-1994 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Baker Institute: Architect Selection (1 of 2) (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Baker Institute: Architect Selection (2 of 2) (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Baker Institute Leadership Committee, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Baker Institute Leadership Committee, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Baker Institute Building Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Baker Institute Annual Conferences, 1995-1996 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Baker Institute Plaza and Fountain, 1995-1997 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Baker Institute: Construction, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Baker Institute: Construction, 1995-1997 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Baker Institute: Dedication, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Baker Institute: Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Athletics: Baseball (Cameron Field, Reckling Park), 1996-1999 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Biology, Geology, Space Science Alterations (Photos), 1996 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - George R. Brown Hall, 1988-1993 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Chemistry Building Renovation, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Cohen House, 1989-2000 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Cohen House, 2003-2004 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Planning and Budgets, 1991-1993 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Planning and Budgets, 1994-1997 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Gardiner and Theobald Budget, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Initial Expenses (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Architect Selection (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Kendall/Heaton Associates, 1993-1997 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Lott Builders, Brown & Root (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Computational Engineering Building: Fund-Raising (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Computational Engineering Building: John Outram Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Computational Engineering Building: John Outram Designs (1 of 2) (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Computational Engineering Building: John Outram Designs (2 of 2) (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Computational Engineering Building: John Outram Photographs (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Fondren Library/Dull Butcher Hall: Planning Documents, 1992-1995 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Fondren Library/Dell Butcher Hall: Planning, 1993-1994 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Fondren Library/Humanities: Planning, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Fondren Library: Planning, 1989-1993 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Fondren Library: Planning Committee, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Fondren Library: Planning, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Fondren Library: Planning, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Fondren Library: Renovation, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Fondren Library: Collection Analysis, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Football: Practice Field (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Humanities: Building, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Jones School: Building Planning, 1993-1999 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Jones School: Steering Committee (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Jones School: Steering Committee (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Jones School: Faculty, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Jones School: Dean Search, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Jones School: Robert A.M. Stern and Morris Architects (1 of 2) (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Jones School: Robert A.M. Stern and Morris Architects (2 of 2) (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Jones School: Kallmann McKinnell & Wood, Architects (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Jones School: Hillier Group, Architects (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Jones School: Luckenbach/Ziegelman Architects (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Jones School: Iconography, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Jones School, 1976-1990 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Jones School: Computing, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Jones School: External Review, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Jones School: Finances, Budgets, 1982-2002 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Martel College (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Mechanical Lab Renovation, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Nanotechnology (Dell Butcher): Planning, Fund-Raising, 1993-1997 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Nanotechnology (Dell Butcher): Construction and Dedication (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Nanotechnology (Dell Butcher): Antoine Predock, Architect (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Nanotechnology (Dell Butcher): Building Design, Photographs (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - O'Connor House, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Rice Stadium (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Rice Stadium: Fitness Center, Weight Room (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Ryon Lab, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Sewall Cut Gallery, 1988-1990 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Shepherd School: Construction, 1987-1993 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Shepherd School: Edythe Bates Old Organ Hall, 1992-1996 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Shepherd School: Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Space Science: Building Remodel, 1996-1997 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Student Center (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Wiess College: Renovation, 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Wiess College: Renovation, 1996-2000 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Off-Campus Buildings
    - Grad House (6600 Main), 1983-1996 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Property Purchase, 1996 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Student Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Tax Information (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Financing (1 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Financing (2 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Financing (3 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Financing (4 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Financing (5 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Century Development Proposal, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Correspondence, 1996-1997-08 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Correspondence, 1997-08-1997-12 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Correspondence, 1998-2007 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Master Lease Agreement (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Ground-Breaking and Dedication, 1998-1999 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Management Contract, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Graduate Apartments (Bissonnet): Shuttle Bus (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Shakespeare: Graduate Apartments, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - #18 Sunset Boulevard, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Weiss House (President's House): Renovation, 1990-1997 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Weiss House (President's House): Renovation, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Weiss House (President's House): Renovation, 2000-2004 (Box 121, Folder 16)